const stuff = [
  { question: "0 + 10", answer: "10" },
  { question: "1 + 10", answer: "11" },
  { question: "2 + 10", answer: "12" },
  { question: "3 + 10", answer: "13" },
  { question: "4 + 10", answer: "14" },
  { question: "5 + 10", answer: "15" },
  { question: "6 + 10", answer: "16" },
  { question: "7 + 10", answer: "17" },
  { question: "8 + 10", answer: "18" },
  { question: "9 + 10", answer: "19" },
  { question: "10 + 10", answer: "20" },
  { question: "11 + 10", answer: "21" },
  { question: "12 + 10", answer: "22" },
  { question: "13 + 10", answer: "23" },
  { question: "14 + 10", answer: "24" },
  { question: "15 + 10", answer: "25" },
  { question: "16 + 10", answer: "26" },
  { question: "17 + 10", answer: "27" },
  { question: "18 + 10", answer: "28" },
  { question: "19 + 10", answer: "29" },
  { question: "20 + 10", answer: "30" },
  { question: "21 + 10", answer: "31" },
  { question: "22 + 10", answer: "32" },
  { question: "23 + 10", answer: "33" },
  { question: "24 + 10", answer: "34" },
  { question: "25 + 10", answer: "35" },
  { question: "26 + 10", answer: "36" },
  { question: "27 + 10", answer: "37" },
  { question: "28 + 10", answer: "38" },
  { question: "29 + 10", answer: "39" },
  { question: "30 + 10", answer: "40" },
  { question: "31 + 10", answer: "41" },
  { question: "32 + 10", answer: "42" },
  { question: "33 + 10", answer: "43" },
  { question: "34 + 10", answer: "44" },
  { question: "35 + 10", answer: "45" },
  { question: "36 + 10", answer: "46" },
  { question: "37 + 10", answer: "47" },
  { question: "38 + 10", answer: "48" },
  { question: "39 + 10", answer: "49" },
  { question: "40 + 10", answer: "50" },
  { question: "41 + 10", answer: "51" },
  { question: "42 + 10", answer: "52" },
  { question: "43 + 10", answer: "53" },
  { question: "44 + 10", answer: "54" },
  { question: "45 + 10", answer: "55" },
  { question: "46 + 10", answer: "56" },
  { question: "47 + 10", answer: "57" },
  { question: "48 + 10", answer: "58" },
  { question: "49 + 10", answer: "59" },
  { question: "50 + 10", answer: "60" },
];

export default stuff;
